在亲兄弟面前  你选择与恶魔为伍
You chose a demon over your own brother,
看看发生了什么
And look what happened.
是我干的  我触发了天启并释放了路西法
I did it. i started the apocalypse, and i set lucifer free.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我会献出任何东西  任何
I would give anything... anything...
能回到从前
To take it all back.
我知道你会的
I know you would.
如果你和我  是拍档的话
If we're gonna be a team, you and i,
一定要互相体谅
It has to be a two-way street.
只要搞定我们面前的拦路虎
We got to just grab on to whatever's in front of us,
干掉它  结束这场战争
Kick its ass, and go down fighting.
我接受这建议
I can get on board with that.
(阿莱恩斯  内布拉斯加州)
我告诉过你应该上床睡觉了
I told you to go to bed.
不行啊  因为我已经死了
I can't. i'm dead.
这是什么  番茄酱吗
What is this -- ketchup?
真恶心
Gross!
你可真无聊
Ow! you're mean.
你爸妈付钱就是叫我来对付你的
Yeah, that's what your parents pay me for -- to be mean.
现在快去睡觉
Bed -- now!
好吧好吧
Okay, okay.
等等
Just wait. wait.
如果让我摸下你的胸  我就去睡
I'll go to bed if you let me touch your boob.
快去睡觉
Oh! go!
我送安珀回家
I'll, uh, take Amber home.
别等我了
Don't wait up.
安珀
Amber.
Amber?
弗朗辛
Francine!!
裴吉探员和派莱特探员
Agents page and plant, FBI
先生们  有什么事吗
Gentlemen. what brings you by?
我们要看安珀·格里尔的尸体
We need to see Amber Greer's body.
真的吗  看这干嘛
Really? what for?
警方报告上说有东西把她开了瓢
The police report said something clawed through her skull?
你们没读过验尸报告吗
You didn't read the autopsy report
我今天早上就发给你们了
That i e-mailed out this morning?
我们的服务器有问题
W-we had, uh, server issues.
他们把她带来时
When they brought her in,
我们以为她被狼或其他什么袭击了
We thought she was attacked by a wolf or something.
其他什么
Or something.
但我们错了
But we were wrong.
那是
Is that a --
这是一片受压变形的指甲
It's a press-on nail.
我们在她的颞叶上发现的
We found it in her temporal lobe.
这可能吗
Is that even possible?
等等  你是不是说这是她自己做的
Wait, are you -- you saying that she did this to herself?
她把自己脑袋给抓破了
Uh-huh. she scratched her brains out.
这得花点时间  痛不欲生
It'd take hours, and it'd hurt like hell,
但肯定  这是有可能的
But sure -- it's possible.
那怎么做
How?
看看你们的简称  民防局  医疗保障
Pick your acronym... OCD PCP
这些都叫做"发疯"
It all spells "crazy."
我猜是某种幻觉上身
My guess -- some kind of phantom itch.
一个很极端的案例
I mean, an extreme case, but...
幻觉搔痒
Phantom itch?
是的
Yeah.
有人一谈到痒
All it takes is someone talking about an itch --
或者一想到它
Or thinking about one, even --
突然间你就忍不住想抓痒
And suddenly you can't stop scratching.
谢谢  医生
Thanks, Doc.
现在  有些问题也许会有点奇怪
Okay, now, some of these questions might seem a bit odd,
但请与我配合
But please just bear with me.
你注意到屋子有变冷吗
Have you noticed any cold spots in the house?
没有
Uh...no.
好的  那有没有奇怪的味道
Okay, uh, what about strange smells?
你在找什么
What're you lookin' for?
还不知道
Don't know yet.
是吉米对吗
It's, uh... Jimmy, right?
安珀是你的保姆吗
So, Amber was your babysitter?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
我的大多数保姆都糟透了
Yeah, most of my babysitters sucked.
尤其是克兰西小姐
Especially Ms. Chancey.
她只关心两件事
She only cared about two things --
“神龙祖玛”和睡觉时间
"dynasty" and bedtime.
那晚你见过什么奇怪的事吗
Did you, uh, you see anything strange that night?
没有
No, sir.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
如果我发现什么  我会告诉你
I-i would tell you if i knew something.
我百分之百答应你
I promise -- 100%.
以我的灵魂起誓
Cross my heart.
好吧  吉米
Well, Jimmy, i, uh...
我知道你在撒谎
...i happen to know you're lying.
我没有
I'm not.
我们来说说真心话吧
We gonna start talking truth,
否则你和我就要去市中心逛逛了
Or are you and me gonna have to take a little trip downtown?
那小孩说他在保姆的梳子里放了这个
Kid said he put this on the babysitter's hairbrush.
迪恩  一般的搔痒是没有办法
Dean, there's no way itching powder
使这女孩把脑给抓破
Made that girl scratch her brains out.
这只是些碾碎的枫树种子
It's just ground-up maple seeds.
如果你有些其他的想法  和他们去说吧
If you have any other theories, i'm open to them.
好  我们马上就到
Yeah, we'll be right there.
发生了什么
What happened?
那人触电死了
Guy got electrocuted.
知道怎么回事吗
Any idea how?
也许是电线外漏
Eh, maybe a loose wire
或者设备短路
Or a piece of equipment shorted out.
到现在  我们还没找到任何线索
So far, we haven't found anything.
目击者呢
Witnesses?
在那里  斯坦利先生
Yeah, guy in there -- Mr. Stanley.
他说他看到了
He says he saw it,
但是他闭口不谈
But he's not making a lick of sense.
人老珠黄了
Senile.
多谢
Thanks.
斯坦利先生
Um, Mr. Stanley?
这是个玩笑
It was just a joke.
我不知道那东西会起作用
I didn't know it would really work.
什么起作用
What would work?
我所做的
All i did...
就是和他握手
Was shake his hand.
准备好了吗
You ready?
一切就绪  巫师先生
Hit it, Mr. Wizard.
真成猪肉了
That'll do, pig.
搞什么名堂
What the hell?
这垃圾应该没这么大能耐啊
That crap isn't supposed to work.
连电池也省了
This thing doesn't even have batteries.
这算什么
So...so, what?
我们找到了一个被诅咒的东西
Are -- are we looking at cursed objects?
也不错啊
Sounds good.
这镇上还有个魔法女巫也说不定
Maybe there's a powerful witch in town.
欢乐蜂鸣器和瘙痒粉
Is there any link between the, uh,
有没有什么联系
The joy buzzer and the itching powder?
一个产自中国  另一个是墨西哥
Uh, one was made in China, the other Mexico,
不过都在同一个地方进货
But they were both bought from the same store.
萨姆
Sam!
欢迎来到conjurarium
Welcome to the conjurarium,
神秘和魔幻的圣地
Sanctum of magic and mystery.
你是店长
You the owner?
是的
Yep.
最近你卖出过瘙痒粉和欢乐蜂鸣器没
You sold any itching powder or joy buzzers lately?
有  每样都卖出去一份
Yeah, a grand total of one of each.
他们可买不起高价货
They aren't exactly big-ticket items.
你们是来买东西的
Look, you boys here to buy something
还是另有他事
Or...what?
这么说  你这里生意很好
So, you get many customers?
孩子们喜欢来这儿
Kids come in.
但他们不会买太多
They don't buy much,
他们更喜欢一些暴力的东西
But they're more than happy to break stuff.
现在他们只关心他们的苹果手机
These days, all they care about are their iphones
还有那些吸血鬼和接吻的电影
And those kissing-vampire movies.
这让我太
The whole thing makes me just...
愤怒
Angry?
对  对  愤怒
Yeah. Yeah, I am angry.
我苦心经营这家店20余年
This shop has been my life for 20 years,
而今它却分文不值了
And now it's wasting away to nothing.
所以你就恨他们
Which is why you hate them.
是的
I suppose.
你就希望你得干点什么
You wish there was something you could do about it.
是的
Yeah, I guess I do.
然后  你就用这个
So you're taking revenge...
报复他们
...with this.
我猜这位老兄不是那个巫师
Something tells me this guy is not a powerful witch.
抱歉
Sorry.
我把这颗牙齿放在你枕头下面
I'll just slip this tooth under your pillow,
在你睡着后
And while you're asleep,
牙仙就会下凡
The tooth fairy will float down
向你拿走一颗犬牙
And swap it out for a quarter.
我睡着后一些怪物就会来我的房间
So some freak is gonna come in my room while I'm sleeping
拿走我的牙齿吗
And take my tooth?
真可怕
Sounds scary.
谢谢  我不用了
No, thank you.
别担心了
Come on.
晚安  小甜心
Good night, sweetie.
别乱动
Hold still.
就像被轻轻地
You might feel just a little...
掐了一下
Pinch.
我呢  很感谢你
Well, I, uh, appreciate that,
佛里蒙特护士
Nurse...Fremont.
请叫我珍
Please -- call me "Jen."
噢  你叫珍
Oh. "Jen" it is.
没牙的这家伙怎样了  口腔里的都差不多没了
What's up with toothless? Cavity creeps get ahold of him?
嗯 差不多
Yeah. Close.
这是他写下来的描述
He wrote up a description --
身高五尺一寸  体重350磅
5'10", 350 pounds,
有翅膀  身穿粉红芭蕾舞裙
Wings, and a pink tutu.
貌似是牙仙
Said it was the tooth fairy.
他确实被止痛药整得一塌糊涂了
So he's obviously whacked out on painkillers.
可能吧
Maybe.
不管怎么说  它都是在没触动到防盗装置
Whatever it was got past locked doors and windows
就能进入到门窗锁着的房间的
Without triggering the alarm.
有没有搞错  牙仙
Come on. The tooth fairy?
并且还在他枕头底下留下了
And it left 32 quarters underneath his pillow --
32颗犬牙
One for each tooth.
好吧  我看你是疯了而且还要给你来点更猛的
Well, I will see your crazy and raise you some.
楼下有几个小孩儿胃溃烂了
There's a couple of kids upstairs with stomach ulcers --
他们把跳跳糖混了可乐一起喝了(大人骗小孩这样会爆炸)
Say they got it from mixing pop rocks and coke.
还有一个人
Another guy...
他的脸很恐怖
His face froze that way.
怎么个恐怖法
What way?
他这个表情  僵持了很久  一动不动
He, uh, held it too long, and it -- it stuck.
他们准备为他做个整形手术
They're flying in a plastic surgeon.
如果你这么说的话
So, I mean, if you add all that up...
我无语了
I got nothing.
我觉得真的有海底小精灵
I thought sea-monkeys were real.
是啊  他们就是丰年虾
They are. They're brine shrimp.
不是  不是  我是说像广告里说的那样
No, no, no, I mean like in the ads.
海猿妈妈在家里炖着肉
You know, like the sea-monkey wife cooks the pot roast
等着海猿爸爸
For the sea-monkey husband,
海猿宝宝就跟小狗一起玩
And the sea-monkey kids play with the dog
在海猿城堡里  这些都是真的
In a sea-monkey castle -- real.
当时我才6岁  不过我全信
I mean, I was 6, but I believed it.
好吧
Okay.
重点是
Point is...
可能这其中有某些联系
Maybe that's the connection.
牙仙  跳跳糖混可乐
The tooth fairy, the pop rocks and coke,
还有欢乐蜂鸣器
The joy buzzer that shocks you --
这些都是假的  但孩子们信
They're all lies that kids believe.
现在这些却都成真了
And now they're coming true.
好  不管是什么促成的  这就是重造现实
Okay, so whatever's doing this is -- is reshaping reality.
它能做上帝会做的事儿
It has the powers of a god.
或是  魔术师的活儿
Or...of a trickster.
对  还有9岁小屁孩的幽默感
Yeah, with the sense of humor of a 9-year-old.
或你
Or you.
老哥  说真的  你怎么还在吃那个火腿
Dude, seriously -- still with the ham?
我们没冰箱啊
We don't have a fridge.
我发现了一些东西
Well I found something.
看
Here.
牙仙攻击了这里
Um, tooth fairy attack was here,
吃跳跳糖和可乐的在这儿
Pop rocks and coke was here,
然后你找到了瘙痒粉
Then you've got itching powder,
恐怖的脸和conjurarium
face freeze, and conjurarium.
都在这2英里范围内
All located within a 2-mile radius.
我们进入了一个离奇爆炸地带
So, we got a blast zone of weird,
在里面幻想会成真
And inside, fantasy becomes reality.
貌似是这样
Looks like.
有什么力量在它中心地带
And what's the a-bomb at its center?
四英亩的农田和一栋房子
Four acres of farmland... and a house.
我们的旅馆可能不在那个圈子里
Our motel isn't in that circle, by any chance?
为什么呢
Why?
天哪  兄弟
Oh, d-dude --
那不是我想的那样  不是吗
That's not what i think it is, is it?
我无聊了  那个护士很火辣
I got bored. that nurse was hot.
你知道你也可能因此失明的
You know you can go blind from that, too.
给我五分钟  我们去查下那房子
Give me five minutes. we'll go check out that house.
对了  不要用我的剃须刀
Hey, do not use my razor!
有什么我能帮你的吗
Can i help you?
你好  你叫什么名字
Hi. uh, what's your name?
你们是谁
Who wants to know?
这个
The, uh...
联邦调查局
...fbi.
让我看看那个
Let me see that.
怎么你们这些家伙都不敲门的
So, what, you guys don't knock?
你父母在家吗
Are your parents home?
他们在工作
They work.
好吧  你介意我们问你一些问题吗
Well, you mind if we ask you a few questions,
可能还要检查下周围的房子
Maybe take a look around the house?
我不知道
I don't know.
别这样  你应该相信我们
Come on. you can trust us.
我们是官员
We're the authorities.
那是什么
What's that?
它叫汤
It's called soup.
你把它加热  然后喝了它
You heat it up, and you eat it.
对的  我知道  只是
Right. i-i know. it's just, um...
在我小时候我也常为自己做主食
I used to make my own dinner, too, when i was a kid.
好吧  我可不是小孩
Well, i'm not a kid.
好  不是  我知道
Right. no, i-i know.
顺便说下  我是罗伯特
I'm robert, by the way.
杰西
Jesse.
杰西  很高兴见到你
Jesse, nice to meet you.
这个是你画的吗
Did you draw this?
它是牙仙
It's the tooth fairy.
那是你想象的牙仙的样子吗
That's what you think the tooth fairy looks like, huh?
我爸爸告诉我的
Yeah. my dad told me about him.
怎么了  难道你爸爸没有告诉过你关于牙仙的事吗
What, didn't your dad tell you about the tooth fairy?
我爸爸
My dad?
我爸告诉我各种各样的传说
My dad told me different stories.
牙仙可不是一个传说
Well, the tooth fairy isn't a story.
杰西  你知道痒粉是什么吗
What do you know about itching powder, jesse?
那东西会让你抓烂自己的脑袋
That stuff will make you scratch your brains out.
跳跳糖和可乐
Pop rocks and coke?
你混合它们  然后你就该进医院和生命说再见了
You mix them, and you'll end up in the hospital.
每个人都知道那个
Everyone knows that.
你不应该拥有那个
You shouldn't have that.
为什么不能
Why not?
它会电死你的
It can electrocute you.
事实上  它不能
Actually, it can't.
它只是个发条玩具
It's just a wind-up toy.
完全没伤害的
It's totally harmless.
甚至没有电池的
Doesn't even have batteries.
所以它不会电击到你
So, it can't shock you?
不  完全不会
Nope. not at all.
我发誓
I swear.
好吧
Okay.
我的意思是它能做的一切只是握在你手上
I mean, all it does is just shake in your hand.
有点蹩脚
It's kind of lame.
看着
See?
你能再说一次你的名字吗
What did you say your name was, again?
哥们  怎么回事
Dude, what the hell?
我有一种直觉  我感受得到它
I had a hunch. i went with it.
-你因为直觉拿我冒险  - 你没事啊
- You risked my ass on a hunch? - You're fine.
还有现在我们知道是谁弄得这个镇团团转
Besides, now we know who's turning this town into willy wonk
这个孩子
The kid.
正是  所有事杰西都相信会成真
Yeah. everything jesse believes comes true.
他认为牙仙长得像贝鲁西
He thinks the tooth fairy looks like belushi,
欢乐蜂鸣器真的会电击到人
Joy buzzers really shock people.
隆的一声  那就是前些天发生的事
Boom. that's what happens.
但是要让他相信欢乐蜂鸣器并不会真的起作用
Yeah, but convince him the joy buzzers don't actually work,
然后他们就会从杀人机器倒回到废物玩具
And they go from killing machines back into crap toys.
他可能甚至不知道他在做这个
He probably doesn't even know he's doing it.
他是怎样做到的
How is he doing it?
找到一些杰西的资料
So, dug up what i could on jesse turner.
不是很多
It's not much.
是学生  赢得过去年的松木比赛
Uh, "b" student, won last year's pinewood derby.
但是看看这个
But get this.
杰西是被领养的
Jesse was adopted.
他的出身资料被密封着
His birth records are sealed.
所以你拆封了它们还是什么
So you unsealed them, and...?
这里没有列出父亲
There's no father listed,
但是杰西的亲生母亲叫朱莉娅·赖特
But jesse's biological mom is named julia wright.
她生活在麋鹿港  这个州的另一边
She lives in elk creek, on the other side of the state.
不管你推销的是什么  我都没有兴趣
Whatever you're selling, i'm not interested.
我们不是推销员
We're not salesmen.
裴吉探员和派莱特探员
Agents page and plant, fbi.
把你的证件塞进门缝里
Put your badge in the slot.
还有你搭档的
Your partner's, too.
你们想要干吗
What do you want?
谢谢
Thank you.
我们只是有些关于你儿子的问题
We just had a few questions... about your son.
我没有儿子
I don't have a son.
他出生在1998年3月29日的奥马哈
He was born march 29, 1998, in omaha.
你把他给人领养了
You put him up for adoption?
他怎么了
What about him?
我们只是觉得有点奇怪
We were just wondering -- um, was it a...
那是一个正常的孕育吗
...was it a normal pregnancy?
有没有什么奇怪的事情发生
Was there anything strange?
走开
Stay away!
等等  赖特太太
Mrs. wright, wait!
我们只想和你聊聊
We just want to talk!
你们不是恶魔
You're not demons?
你怎么知道有恶魔这回事
How do you know about demons?
我被附身过
I was possessed.
恶魔控制我身体  伤害人们
A demon took control of my body, and I hurt people.
我杀了人
I killed people.
杀人的不是你
That -- that wasn't you.
但我在场
But I was there.
我听到一个女人向我求饶
I heard a woman beg for mercy.
感觉到年轻女孩的鲜血从我手中淌下
I...felt a young girl's blood drip down my hands.
你是怎么知道用盐的
That's how you knew about the salt.
是啊  我学了些技巧  恶魔控制了我好几个月
Yeah, I picked up tricks. It was in my head for months.
几个月
How many months?
9个月
Nine.
那么你的儿子
So your son...
是啊  所有阶段
Yeah -- the whole time.
怀孕  生产
The pregnancy, birth --
整个孕育过程
All of it.
我都被附身
I was possessed.
孩子出生的那晚  我独自一人
The night the baby was born, I was alone.
那种痛楚  让我痛不欲生
And the pain was -- the pain was overwhelming.
我大声尖叫  却变成了一阵狂笑
I-I screamed, and it came out a laugh...
因为恶魔很开心
Because the demon was happy.
它利用我的身体来孕育孩子
It used my body to give birth to a child.
等孩子出生后  变得不一样了
When it was over, something changed.
也许是恶魔累了
Maybe the -- the demon was tired
也可能是阵痛让我战胜了它
Or if the pain helped me fight it, but...
但不知怎么地  我又被附身了
...Somehow, I took control.
恶魔在我体内悲叹
And the demon wailed inside me.
不断地击打着我的头骨
It pounded against my skull.
我感到自己的头就快裂了
I thought my head was gonna explode.
但  突然之间灵光一闪
But...I knew.
我知道我该怎么做
I knew what I had to do.
当我和孩子独处时
And when I was alone with the baby...
体内有种声音
A part of me...
让我杀了他
Part of me wanted to kill it.
但  老天救救我  我不能这么做
But, god help me, I couldn't do that.
所以我只能把孩子给人收养
So...I put it up for adoption...
然后逃得远远的
And I ran.
孩子的父亲是谁
Who was the father?
我还是处女
I was a virgin.
你们见过我儿子吗
Have you seen my son?
是个人吗
Is he human?
他叫杰西
His name's Jesse.
住在阿莱恩斯
He lives in, uh,live in alliance.
是个好孩子
He's a good kid.
现在怎么办
So, now what?
得去找帮手
We need help.
看来你收到我们的消息了
I take it you got our message.
你们能找到那男孩真是幸运
It's lucky you found the boy.
是啊  非常幸运
Oh, yeah, real lucky.
我们该怎么处置他
What do we do with him?
杀了他
Kill him.
卡西
Cass.
这孩子半人半魔
This child is half demon and half human,
但他比人和魔都要强大
But it's far more powerful than either.
其他文明管他叫混合坎比翁或是犬夜叉
Other cultures call this hybrid cambion or katako.
你知道他是异教徒
You know him as the antichrist.
不是我放的
That wasn't me.
谁把那玩意放那里了
Who put that there?
总之  我有点不懂
Anyways, I don't get it.
杰西是恶魔的儿子吗
Jesse is the devil's son?
不是  当然不是
No, of course not.
你们的圣经错的太多了
Your bible gets more wrong than it does right.
异教徒并不是路西法的信徒
The antichrist is not lucifer's child.
不过是恶魔之子罢了
It's just demon spawn.
但却是恶魔在与天使之战中
But it is one of the devil's greatest weapons
最强大的武器
In the war against heaven.
要是杰西是恶魔的重要武器
Well, if jesse's a demonic howitzer,
那他在内布拉斯加州干什么
Then what the hell's he doing in nebraska?
他被恶魔弄丢了  恶魔找不到他
The demons lost him. They can't find him.
但他们正在努力寻找
But they're looking.
他们为什么会弄丢他
And they lost him because...?
因为孩子的力量
Because of the child's power.
使天使和恶魔都无法找到他
It hides him from both angels and demons.
不过只是暂时
For now.
就像是他周围有个磁场
So he's got, like, a force field around him.
那太好了  问题解决了
Well, that's great. Problem solved.
随着路西法的苏醒  这孩子会越来越强大
With lucifer risen, this child grows strong.
不用多久  他就
Soon, he will do more
不仅仅只是让一些玩具成真
Than just make a few toys come to life --
而是会做些将恶魔引向他的事
Something that will draw the demons to him.
恶魔最终将会找到他
The demons will find this child.
路西法能随心改造他
Lucifer will twist this boy to his purpose.
然后  只需一个字
And then, with a word,
这孩子就能杀死众天使
This child will destroy the host of heaven.
哇哇哇  等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait.
你是说  杰西将会是对付天使的核武器
You're saying that -- that jesse's gonna nuke the angels?
我们决不允许此事发生
We cannot allow that to happen.
等等
Wait.
我们都是好人
We're the good guys.
不能杀小孩
We -- we don't just kill children.
一年前
A year ago,
是你的不顾一切让他们有机会赢得这场战争
You would have done whatever it took to win this war.
情况不同了
Things change.
好了  听着  我们不去杀他好吗
Okay. hey, look, we are not going to kill him. all right?
但我们也不能把杰西留在这  这点我们都清楚
But we can't leave jesse here either. we know that.
所以
So...
我们带他去鲍比那里  他知道该怎么办
We take him to bobby's. he'll know what to do.
你是要绑架他吗
You'll kidnap him?
小镇上发生的事
What is going on in this town,
都是在孩子高兴的情况下发生的
It's what happens when this thing is happy.
要是把他惹火了  后果将不堪设想
You cannot imagine what it will do if it's angry.
此外  你准备怎么扣留他
Besides, how will you hold him?
他能立刻跑到世界另一端
With a thought, he could be halfway around the world.
那我们
So we --
我们告知他真相
So we tell him the truth.
你说杰西注定会成为敌对方  没关系
You say jesse's destined to go dark side -- fine.
但他现在还没
But he hasn't yet.
所以既然一切都在于他
So if we lay it all out for him --
在于他会在哪一方  天启  无数的可能
What he is, the apocalypse, everything --
也许他会做出正确的选择
He might make the right choice.
你就没有
You didn't.
而我不会再冒险了
And I can't take that chance.
该死的
Damn it.
抱歉  不好意思
Sorry. I'm sorry.
别怕  你没事吧
It's -- it's no worries. you okay?
没事  不过是今天受了点  刺激
Yeah. it's just today -- a little...shaky.
噢  是因为温切斯特两兄弟的话吗
Ah. well, talking to the Winchesters will do that to you.
还记得我吗  亲爱的
Don't you recognize me, sweetheart?
当时我们处得挺愉快的  不是吗
We had some great times together, didn't we?
直到你偷偷的带走人  还把它藏了起来
And then you stole something from us, hid it away.
你可真是太  太顽皮了
That was very, very naughty of you.
所以我们只好守株待兔  静观其变
So we watched, and we waited.
直到如今
And now...
他们告诉你地址了  对吗
They told you where he is, didn't they?
是时候该去拜访下咱俩的儿子了
I think it's time we go and visit our son.
别怕
Don't be afraid.
我不会伤害你的
I won't hurt you.
妈妈  爸爸
Mom! dad!
你父母已经睡着了
Your mother and father are sleeping.
我可以肯定地告诉你  不到天亮他们是不会醒的
I assure you, they won't wake until morning.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
是不是有人在
Was there a guy here?
穿着风衣
In a trench coat?
他是你朋友
Was he your friend?
他
Him?
不是
No.
是我干的
I did that.
但我是怎么办到的呢
But how did I do that?
你是个超级英雄
You're a superhero.
我
I am?
对
Yeah.
当然是你  除了你还有谁可以将人变成玩具小人
Yeah. I mean, who else could turn someone into a toy?
你就是超人
You're superman --
就只少了披风和马靴这些装备罢了
Minus the cape and the go-go boots.
听着  我搭档和我
See, my -- my partner and I,
效力于一个秘密的政府机构
We work for a secret government agency.
工作就是找寻拥有超能力的孩子
It's our job to find kids with special powers.
老实说  我们来这儿就是要带你
In fact, we're here to take you
到位于南达科塔州的秘密基地去
To a hidden base in south dakota,
让你有机会惩恶扬善
Where you'll be trained to fight evil.
就像<变种特工>那样
Like the x-men?
就是<变种特工>那样
Exactly like the x-men.
老实说  我们带你去见的家伙
In fact, the, uh, guy we're taking you to --
恰好也是坐轮椅的
He's even in a wheelchair.
你将成为一名英雄
You'll be a hero.
你将救助民众  将抱得美人归
You'll save lives. you'll get the girl.
听上去就很诱人  对吗
Sounds like fun, right?
他们逗你玩呢
They're lying to you.
乖乖蹲角落去吧  编剧大师们
Stay right there, dreamboat.
编故事确实能避免流血
Can't hurt you.
然而
Orders.
你们的掉以轻心
You, on the other hand?
聪明反被聪明误了
Hurting you's encouraged.
放了他
Leave him alone!
杰西
Jesse.
你长得真漂亮
You're beautiful.
继承了你父亲的眼睛
You have your father's eyes.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是你母亲
I'm your mother.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
你有一半的人类血统
You're half human...
也有一半我们的血统
Half one of us.
她说得是恶魔  杰西
She means demons, Jesse!
被你称为父母的那两个人
Those people you call your parents --
他们也骗了你
They lied to you, too.
你不是他们的孩子  不是亲生
You're not theirs -- not really.
但爸爸妈妈他们爱我
My mom and dad love me.
是吗
Do they?
原来他们整天把你一个人晾家里
Is -- is that why they leave you alone all day?
正是因为他们爱你
Because they love you so much?
那些家伙  那些骗子
These people -- these imposters --
他们跟你说过牙仙是真的吗
They told you that the tooth fairy was real
他们警告过你那个玩具会伤害你吗
And that your toys could hurt you
他们告诉过你还有成千上万的事都是假的吗
And a hundred other things that aren't true.
他们是非常爱你  所以打造了个满是谎言的世界给你
They love you so much, they made your whole life a lie.
别再自欺欺人了  杰西
Look into your heart, Jesse.
其实你早就知道自己非他们所生
You've always known you weren't theirs.
你早就知道自己有多么的特别
You've always known you were different.
他们全都在骗你
Everyone has lied to you.
他们不是联邦探员
They're not FBI agents.
你也不是什么超级英雄
And you're not a superhero.
那我是什么
Then what am I?
你很强大
You're powerful.
你无所不能
You can have anything you want.
更可以为所欲为
You can do anything you want.
别听他的
Don't listen to him!
他们只会把你当个孩子骗
They treated you like a child.
从来没人信任你  他们全都只会骗你
Nobody trusted you. everybody's lied to you.
难道你不生气吗
Doesn't that make you angry?
瞧瞧  你对此很生气嘛
See? it does make you angry.
但我对你说的全是事实  杰西
But I'm telling you the truth, Jesse.
如果这世上没有了谎言不是会更好吗
Wouldn't it be better if there were no lies?
跟着我
Come with me...
你就将有机会净化整个世界
And you can wash it all clean.
让一切重头再来
Start over.
想象一下
Imagine that --
一个没有谎言的世界
A world without lies.
她说的对  我们是欺骗了你
She's right. we lied to you.
但我会告诉你真正的事实
But I'll tell you the truth.
我只不过是  想  想告诉
I just want...to tell...
住手
Stop it.
我想听听他想说什么
I want to hear what he has to say.
你已经强大地超出我想象了
You're stronger than I thought.
我们是骗了你
We lied to you.
对不起
And I'm sorry.
现在澄清下
So here's the truth.
我叫萨姆·温彻斯特
I'm Sam Winchester.
他是我哥哥  迪恩
That's my brother, Dean.
我们是猎魔人
W-we hunt monsters.
而你自己就是恶魔
Except when you are the monster.
是吧  萨姆?
Right, sammy?
站在那儿的女人  她叫茱莉亚
And that woman right there, her name is julia.
她是你母亲
She's your mother.
但现在和你说话的
But the thing inside of her,
是她体内的东西
The thing that you're talking to --
-那是恶魔  - 恶魔
- It's a demon. - A demon?
从你遇见他们那刻起
He's done nothing but lie to you
他们都在骗你
since the moment you met him
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
惩罚他
Punish him.
坐下  闭嘴
Sit down and shut up.
现在有一场
There's, uh, kind of a...
天使与恶魔之间的大战
A war between angels and demons,
而你也参与其中
And... you're a part of it.
我不过是个孩子
I'm just a kid.
如果你愿意  就跟她走吧
You can go with her if you want.
我阻止不了你  没人可以
I can't stop you. no one can.
但如果你这么做
But if you do...
会导致成千上万的人死去
Millions of people will die.
她说我有一半恶魔血统  是真的吗
She said i was half demon. is that true?
没错
Yes.
但你另一半仍是人类
But you're half human, too.
你可以做出正确的选择
You can do the right thing.
决定权在你  杰斯
You've got choices, jesse.
但一旦你选错
But if you make the wrong ones,
你的余生都会后悔莫及
It'll haunt you for the rest of your life.
为何你要告诉我这些
Why are you telling me this?!
因为我相信  就算当时我失败了
Because i have to believe someone can make the right choice,
终究有人能做出正确的选择
Even if i couldn't.
离开她
Get out of her.
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
我只是想着就做到了
I just did.
孩子
Kid...
你太酷了
...you're awesome.
她会没事的吧
Is she gonna be all right?
总会好起来的
Eventually.
听着  事实上
Look, uh, truth is,
他算是我的朋友
He's kind of a buddy of mine.
你有办法把他变回去吗
Is there any way you could turn him back?
他曾试图杀死我
He tried to kill me.
对  嗯
Right. uh...
但他  他是个好人
But he's a -- he's a good guy.
只不过是一念之差
He was just confused.
好吧
Okay.
情况有些复杂  我们回头再谈
It's been a long night. we'll...talk about it later.
现在怎么办
What now?
我们带你去到一个安全的地方
Now we take you someplace safe,
训练你
Get you trained up.
你得投入战斗了  孩子
You'd be handy in a fight, kid.
如果我不想战斗呢
What if i don't want to fight?
杰西
Jesse.
你很强大
You're powerful.
比我们所见过的所有东西
More powerful than...
还要强大得多
Pretty much anything we've ever seen.
-这也让你变成了  - 怪物
- That makes you... - A freak.
对某些人来说  确实如此
To some people, maybe.
但对我们来说不是
But not to us.
瞧  从某种程度上来说  我们也是怪物
See, we're kind of freaks ourselves.
我不能留在这了是吧
I can't stay here, can i?
没错
No.
恶魔知道你在这儿  他们会成群结队地前来
The demons know where you are, and more will be coming.
我不会丢下我的父母
I won't go without my mom and dad.
家人比什么都重要
There's nothing more important than family.
这我们明白
We get that.
如果你真想带上他们
And if you really want to take them with you,
我们也没有意见
We'll back your play.
但是你必须明白
But you got to understand --
这样一来  他们也有危险
It's gonna be dangerous for them, too.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们的父亲
Our dad...
无论他去哪儿  都会带上我们
He would take us with him wherever he went.
-他现在在哪儿  - 他死了
- Where is he now? - Dead.
被恶魔杀死了
A demon killed him.
听着  杰西
Look, Jesse...
一旦你加入了战斗
Once you're in this fight...
就无法再回头
...you're in it till the end,
不论结局是输还是赢
Win or lose.
我该怎么做
What should I do?
我们无法告诉你
We can't tell you.
这得由你自己来选择
It's your choice.
我知道  这不公平
It's not fair. I know.
我能去见见我的父母吗
Can I go see my parents?
我
I, um...
我得和他们告别
I need to...say goodbye.
当然
Sure.
他上去很久了
He's been up there a long time.
他走了
He's gone.
去了哪儿
Where?
我不知道
I don't know.
杰斯把镇子上的人都恢复了原样
Jesse put everyone in town back to normal --
那些受害者都还活着
The ones still alive.
然后他就消失了
Then he vanished.
看啊
Hey.
上面写了什么
What does it say?
他说他必须留下来保护他的父母
That he had to leave to keep his parents safe,
他爱他们  他很抱歉
That he loves them, and he's sorry.
怎样才能找到他
How do we find him?
不行  那孩子具有强大的力量
With the boy's powers, we can't.
除非他自己想要被发现
Not unless he wants to be found.
你觉得呢  杰斯会没事的吧
You think Jesse's gonna be okay?
但愿如此
I hope so.
要知道  我们告诉他真相
You know, we destroyed that kid's life
相当于毁了那孩子的一生
By telling him the truth.
我们别无选择  迪恩
We didn't have a choice, dean.
是啊
Yeah.
知道吗  我好想弄明白
You know, I'm starting to get
为什么父母总是对孩子撒谎了
Why parents lie to their kids.
他们想让孩子相信  在这世上最坏的东西
You want them to believe that the worst thing out there
不过是混合跳跳糖和可乐
Is mixing pop rocks and coke --
这样能保护他们免受真正邪恶的伤害
Protect them from the real evil.
想让他们能安心入睡的话
You want them going to bed feeling safe.
你就必须骗他们  事实如此
If that means lying to them, so be it.
我越是这样想  就越是希望
The more i think about it...
当年爸爸也对我们撒谎该多好
The more i wish dad had lied to us.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me too.